Blinken, Donald M.; Papers apap080
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1969-2003; 3; 2.64 cubic ft.
  - Independent Commission on the Future of SUNY, 1984 June-1984 July (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Independent Commission on the Future of SUNY, 1984 July (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Independent Commission on the Future of SUNY, 1984 August-1984 October (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Independent Commission on the Future of SUNY, 1984 October-1984 December (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Independent Commission on the Future of SUNY, 1985 January (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Independent Commission on the Future of SUNY, 1985 January-1985 February (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Independent Commission on the Future of SUNY, 1985 March (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Independent Commission on the Future of SUNY, 1985 March-1985 April (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Independent Commission on the Future of SUNY, 1985 May-1985 July (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - International Programs, China, 1980-1983 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Investment Planning Review, 1981-1982 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Jewish Forum, 1984 December-1985 January (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Jewish Forum, 1985 February-1985 June (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Legislative Proposal for Public Corporation, 1985 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Moore, Elizabeth, 1969; Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - New York Times Luncheon Meeting, 1987-1988 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - National Commission on Higher Education Issues Report, Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Podhortz, Norman, 1985 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Religious Holidays, Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Report of Chancellor's Task Force on Community Colleges, 1986 July-1986 September (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller Institute for Government, 1980-1988 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller Institute for Government, 1989-1990 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller Institute for Government, 1992-1993 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Salary Issues, 1978-1987 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - State University Plaza, Building Dedication, 1978 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - State University Plaza, Building Dedication Programs, 1978 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - SUNY Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - SUNY Correspondence, 1978-1992 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - SUNY/CUNY, 1976 January-1976 October (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - SUNY/CUNY, 1976 November-1976 December (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - SUNY/CUNY, 1977 January (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - SUNY/CUNY, 1977 February-1977 April (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - SUNY/CUNY, 1977 May-1977 November (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - SUNY/CUNY, 1978 January-1978 September (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - SUNY/CUNY, General Office File, 1978 October-1978 December (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - SUNY/CUNY, General Office File, 1979-1982 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - SUNY/CUNY, General Office File, 1983-1989 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - SUNY/CUNY and New York State Legislation, Regulation, 1982-1986 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - System Business Development Service Office Report, by John Mather, 1987 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Trustee Meetings, 1978-1987 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Trustee Policies and By-Laws, 1978-1979 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Trustee Policies and By-Laws, 1980-1984 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Trustee Policies and By-Laws, 1986-1988 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Trustee Policies (Sexual Orientation and Discrimination), 1980-1983 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Tuition Tax Credits, 1981-1982 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Warren, James J., Retirement, 1982 (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
- SUNY Publications, 1985-1990; 4; 0.33 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically.
  This series consists of publications about SUNY. Topics include the cost of higher education, SUNY's history, the Nelson A. Rockefeller School of Government, and other related matters. Any material related to a report, such as correspondence, is identified in the folder title.
  - The Challenge and the Choice, Undated (Box 1 (4-SUNY Publications), Folder 1)
  - The Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government, 1985 (Box 1 (4-SUNY Publications), Folder 2)
  - SUNY: A Historical Perspective Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (4-SUNY Publications), Folder 3)
  - SUNY: A Historical Perspective, 1989 (Box 1 (4-SUNY Publications), Folder 4)
  - The Cost of Higher Education: An Essay on the Comparative Financing of Universities, 1989 (Box 1 (4-SUNY Publications), Folder 5)
  - SUNY Profiles, 1990 (Box 1 (4-SUNY Publications), Folder 6)
  - SUNY, 2000 (Box 1 (4-SUNY Publications), Folder 7)